A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Institutional Grants and Proposals, 1983-1998; 2
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-15 (Reel 71, Frame 213)
  - University of California, San Diego - General Correspondence (Reel 71, Frame 459)
  - University of California, San Diego - Denied Proposals 84-37, 85-106, 85-138, 85-164, 85-197, 85-236, 86-6, 86-10, 86-27, 86-148, 86-168, 88-1, 89-22, 94-14 (Reel 71, Frame 480)
  - University of California, San Diego - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-42 (Reel 71, Frame 619)
  - University of California, San Diego - Grant 92-6 (Reel 72, Frame 1)
  - University of California, San Francisco - General Correspondence (Reel 72, Frame 333)
  - University of California, San Francisco - Denied Proposals 85-59, 86-13, 86-138, 94-20, 95-13 (Reel 72, Frame 362)
  - University of California, San Francisco - Grant 84-12 (Reel 72, Frame 448)
  - University of California, San Francisco - Grant 88-14 (Reel 72, Frame 691)
  - University of California, San Francisco - Grant 92-2 (Reel 73, Frame 1)
  - University of California, San Francisco - Grant 92-27 (Reel 73, Frame 173)
  - University of California, San Francisco - Grant 96-2 (Reel 73, Frame 322)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Denied Proposals 85-132, 89-40, 90-12 (Reel 73, Frame 354)
  - University of California, Santa Cruz - Research Program Grant - Grant 92-21 (Reel 73, Frame 443)
  - California Biomedical Research Association - Grant 86-5 (Reel 73, Frame 693)
  - California Institute of Technology - Denied Proposals 85-191, 90-54 (Reel 73, Frame 864)
  - California Institute of Technology - Grant 84-4 (Reel 74, Frame 1)
  - California Institute of Technology - Research Program Grant - Grant 86-8 (Reel 74, Frame 194)
  - California Institute of Technology - Research Program Grant, Supplement to Grant 86-8 - Grant 97-5 (Reel 74, Frame 601)
  - California Parkinson's Foundation - General Correspondence (Reel 74, Frame 650)
  - California State University, Hayward - General Correspondence (Reel 74, Frame 655)
  - Cancer Prevention Research Institute - Denied Proposals 93-11, 93-27 (Reel 74, Frame 660)
  - Cancer Research Council - General Correspondence (Reel 74, Frame 746)
  - Cancer Research Institute - Denied Proposal 94-30 (Reel 74, Frame 766)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington - Denied Proposals 85-57, 89-32, 94-32 (Reel 74, Frame 783)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-43 (Reel 74, Frame 836)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington - Grant 97-4 (Reel 74, Frame 973)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University - Denied Proposals 89-10, 94-29 (Reel 75, Frame 1)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University - Research Program Grant - Grant 86-3 (Reel 75, Frame 48)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University - Grant 94-1 (Reel 75, Frame 227)
  - Case Western Reserve University - General Correspondence (Reel 75, Frame 332)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-44 (Reel 75, Frame 338)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Denied Proposals 90-18, 92-29 (Reel 75, Frame 353)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Grant 96-1 (Reel 75, Frame 650)
  - Catholic University of America - Denied Proposal 92-27 (Reel 75, Frame 682)
  - Cedars-Sinai Medical Center - Denied Proposals 85-62, 88-55, 90-49 (Reel 75, Frame 694)
  - Center for Neurochemistry - Denied Proposals 85-199 (Reel 75, Frame 735)
  - University of Central Florida - General Correspondence (Reel 75, Frame 745)
  - Central Institute for the Deaf - General Correspondence (Reel 75, Frame 752)
  - University of Chicago - Research Program Grant - Grant 86-10 (Reel 75, Frame 763)
  - University of Chicago - Grant 93-16 (Reel 76, Frame 1)
  - University of Chicago - Supplement to Grant 86-10 - Grant 97-6 (Reel 76, Frame 199)
  - Chicago Medical School, University of Health Sciences - General Correspondence (Reel 76, Frame 222)
  - Chicago Medical School, University of Health Sciences - Denied Proposals 85-118, 91-28 (Reel 76, Frame 279)
  - Chicago Medical School, University of Health Sciences - Grant 84-13 (Reel 76, Frame 307)
  - Children's Hospital, Boston - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-45 (Reel 76, Frame 442)
  - Children's Hospital, Boston - Grant 92-1 (Reel 76, Frame 702)
  - Children's Hospital, Oakland Research Institute - Denied Proposal 91-17 (Reel 76, Frame 1046)
  - Children's Hospital, Philadelphia - Denied Proposals 89-50, 93-8 (Reel 76, Frame 1059)
  - Children's Hospital of Pittsburgh - General Correspondence (Reel 76, Frame 1087)
  - Children's Hospital of St. Paul - Denied Proposal 88-65 (Reel 76, Frame 1094)
  - Children's Hospital Medical Center, Cincinnati - General Correspondence (Reel 76, Frame 1115)
  - Children's Hospital Medical Center, Cincinnati - Denied Proposals 84-209, 85-27, 88-34 (Reel 77, Frame 1)
  - Children's Hospital Medical Center, Cincinnati - Research Program Grant - Grant 92-22 (Reel 77, Frame 123)
  - Children's Memorial Medical Center - Denied Proposal 93-20 (Reel 77, Frame 439)
  - Children's Memorial Medical Center - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-22 (Reel 77, Frame 476)
  - University of Cincinnati - General Correspondence (Reel 77, Frame 592)
  - University of Cincinnati - Denied Proposals 84-16, 85-31, 85-32, 85-33, 85-34, 87-34, 89-58 (Reel 77, Frame 600)
  - University of Cincinnati - Grant 95-34 (Reel 77, Frame 746)
  - Clemson University - Denied Proposals 85-172, 90-16 (Reel 77, Frame 893)
  - Cleveland Clinic Foundation - Denied Proposal 89-72 (Reel 77, Frame 927)
  - Cleveland Research Institute - Denied Proposal 87-59 (Reel 77, Frame 968)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Denied Proposal 91-14 (Reel 77, Frame 991)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Grant 85-25 (Reel 78, Frame 1)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Grant 86-9 (Reel 78, Frame 142)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Research Program Grant - Grant 91-5 (Reel 78, Frame 322)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder - General Correspondence (Reel 78, Frame 483)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder - Denied Proposals 85-125, 85-179, 85-18, 89-43 (Reel 78, Frame 496)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-1 (Reel 78, Frame 570)
  - University of Colorado, Colorado Springs - Denied Proposal 85-147 (Reel 78, Frame 679)
  - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center, Denver - Denied Proposals 85-183, 86-147, 86-160 (Reel 78, Frame 686)
  - University of Colorado Health Sciences Center, Denver - Research Program Grant - 91-3 (Reel 78, Frame 735)
  - Columbia University - General Correspondence (Reel 79, Frame 1)
  - Columbia University - Denied Proposals 85-237, 86-32, 86-117, 88-74, 91-19, 92-64 (Reel 79, Frame 60)
  - Columbia University - Grant 85-26 (Reel 79, Frame 134)
  - Columbia University - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-59 (Reel 79, Frame 597)
  - Columbia University - Grant 93-15 (Reel 80, Frame 1)
  - Computer Science Research Institute - Denied Proposal 85-88 (Reel 80, Frame 197)
  - University of Connecticut Health Center, Storrs - Denied Proposals 85-239, 90-22 (Reel 80, Frame 217)
  - Conner Davis Study Institute, Inc. - Denied Proposals 84-40, 84-160 (Reel 80, Frame 308)
  - Coriell Institute for Medical Research - Denied Proposal 92-67 (Reel 80, Frame 328)
  - Cornell University - General Correspondence (Reel 80, Frame 350)
  - Cornell University - Denied Proposals 85-128, 85-226, 86-87, 88-36 (Reel 80, Frame 373)
  - Cornell University - Grant 94-2 (Reel 80, Frame 457)
  - Cornell University - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-21 (Reel 80, Frame 601)
  - Cornell University Medical College - Research Program Grant - Grant 92-8 (Reel 80, Frame 728)
  - Creighton University - General Correspondence (Reel 80, Frame 903)
  - Dana-Farber Cancer Institute - Denied Proposal 86-135 (Reel 80, Frame 912)
  - Dana-Farber Cancer Institute - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-2 (Reel 80, Frame 935)
  - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center - Grant 90-15 (Reel 81, Frame 1)
  - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center - Research Program Grant - Grant 94-15 (Reel 81, Frame 58)
  - Dartmouth Medical School - General Correspondence (Reel 81, Frame 237)
  - Deborah Hospital Foundation - Denied Proposal 89-11 (Reel 81, Frame 276)
  - Delegation for Basic Biomedical Research - General Correspondence (Reel 81, Frame 291)
  - Delegation for Basic Biomedical Research - Grant 91-44 (Reel 81, Frame 364)
  - Dermatology Foundation of Miami - Denied Proposal 85-184 (Reel 81, Frame 385)
  - Dermatology Foundation of Miami - Grant 97-3 (Reel 81, Frame 398)
  - Drexel University - Denied Proposals 85-188, 86-31, 91-13 (Reel 81, Frame 416)
  - Duke University - General Correspondence (Reel 81, Frame 474)
  - Duke University - Denied Proposals 85-84, 85-102, 85-243, 86-12, 86-21, 86-81, 86-95, 92-42 (Reel 81, Frame 482)
  - Duke University - Research Program Grant - Grant 90-8 (Reel 81, Frame 564)
  - Duke University - Research Program Grant, Supplement to Grant 90-8 - Grant 97-7 (Reel 81, Frame 805)
  - D'Youville College - Denied Proposal 92-18 (Reel 81, Frame 825)
  - East Carolina University - Denied Proposals 85-83, 85-228 (Reel 81, Frame 845)
  - East Tennessee State University - Denied Proposal 90-4 (Reel 81, Frame 863)
  - EEG Systems Laboratory - General Correspondence (Reel 81, Frame 872)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Institute for Cancer Research - Denied Proposal 94-28 (Reel 81, Frame 885)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Institute for Cancer Research - Grant 86-4 (Reel 81, Frame 896)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Institute for Cancer Research - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-61 (Reel 82, Frame 1)
  - Emory University - General Correspondence (Reel 82, Frame 265)
  - Emory University - Denied Proposals 84-35, 85-40, 87-23 (Reel 82, Frame 274)
  - Emory University - Grant 94-3 (Reel 82, Frame 329)
  - EORTC - General Correspondence (Reel 82, Frame 469)
  - Erdman Clinic - General Correspondence (Reel 82, Frame 481)
  - Eye Research Institute - General Correspondence (Reel 82, Frame 486)
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology (FASEB) - Grant 95-8 (Reel 82, Frame 578)
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology (FASEB) - Grant 97-1 (Reel 82, Frame 621)
  - University of Florida, Gainesville - General Correspondence (Reel 82, Frame 649)
  - University of Florida, Gainesville - Denied Proposals 88-27, 88-53, 89-39, 90-62 (Reel 82, Frame 722)
  - University of Florida, Gainesville - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-13 (Reel 82, Frame 778)
  - Florida Institute of Technology - General Correspondence (Reel 82, Frame 880)
  - Florida International University - Denied Proposals 85-116, 86-90, 88-28 (Reel 82, Frame 889)
  - Florida State University - Research Program Grant - Grant 91-27 (Reel 83, Frame 1)
  - (William Guy) Forbeck Research Foundation - Denied Proposal 90-7 (Reel 83, Frame 291)
  - (William Guy) Forbeck Research Foundation - Grant 88-9 (Reel 83, Frame 331)
  - Fordham University - Denied Proposal 92-63 (Reel 83, Frame 475)
  - Forsyth Dental Center - General Correspondence (Reel 83, Frame 491)
  - Foundation for Biomedical Research - General Correspondence (Reel 83, Frame 517)
  - Four Schools Physician Scientist Program - Grant 92-7 (Reel 83, Frame 551)
  - Fox Chase Cancer Center - Denied Proposals 86-4, 92-61, 95-1 (Reel 83, Frame 974)
  - Fox Chase Cancer Center - Research Program Grant - Grant 91-26 (Reel 84, Frame 1)
  - Friends of Animals, Inc. - General Correspondence (Reel 84, Frame 288)
  - (Olive W.) Garvey Center for the Improvement of Human Functioning, Inc. - Denied Proposal 86-104 (Reel 84, Frame 308)
  - George Washington University - Denied Proposal 92-2 (Reel 84, Frame 342)
  - George Washington University - Grant 95-16 (Reel 84, Frame 351)
  - Georgetown University - Denied Proposals 89-64, 90-35 (Reel 84, Frame 591)
  - Georgetown University - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-20 (Reel 84, Frame 641)
  - Medical College of Georgia - Denied Proposals 86-50, 86-142, 90-57 (Reel 85, Frame 1)
  - University of Georgia, Athens - Denied Proposals 86-24, 92-5 (Reel 85, Frame 87)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital and Medical Center - Denied Proposal 86-91 (Reel 85, Frame 119)
  - Goodwin Institute for Cancer Research - General Correspondence (Reel 85, Frame 148)
  - Grace Cancer Drug Center - Denied Proposal 85-1 (Reel 85, Frame 182)
  - Green College - General Correspondence (Reel 85, Frame 210)
  - Greenwood Genetic Center - Denied Proposal 86-83 (Reel 85, Frame 219)
  - Guthrie Research Institute - Denied Propsal 86-158 (Reel 85, Frame 230)
  - Hahnemann University - Denied Proposals 87-53, 88-32, 89-42 (Reel 85, Frame 243)
  - (Walter and Eliza) Hall Institute of Medical Research - General Correspondence (Reel 85, Frame 326)
  - Harrington Arthritis Research Center - General Correspondence (Reel 85, Frame 345)
  - Harvard Medical School - Denied Proposals 85-19, 85-81, 85-100, 85-131, 85-220, 85-247, 86-40, 86-48, 86-128, 88-17, 88-50, 89-74, 94-40 (Reel 85, Frame 354)
  - Harvard Medical School - Grant 84-5 (Reel 85, Frame 564)
  - Harvard Medical School - Research Program Grant - Grant 88-13 (Reel 85, Frame 714)
  - Harvard Medical School - Grant 92-4 (Reel 86, Frame 1)
  - Harvard University - General Correspondence (Reel 86, Frame 730)
  - Harvard University - Denied Proposals 85-213, 85-229, 86-69, 86-112 (Reel 86, Frame 825)
  - Harvard University - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-15 (Reel 87, Frame 1)
  - Harvard University - Grant 96-3 (Reel 87, Frame 96)
  - Harvard University School of Public Health - Denied Proposals 88-70, 90-77, 96-2 (Reel 87, Frame 130)
  - Harvard University School of Public Health - Research Program Grant - Grant 91-49 (Reel 87, Frame 201)
  - Haverford College - General Correspondence (Reel 87, Frame 495)
  - University of Hawaii, Manoa - Denied Proposals 85-117, 90-8 (Reel 87, Frame 503)
  - Hearing Education and Research Foundation - Denied Proposals 86-63, 86-114, 90-8 (Reel 87, Frame 529)
  - Heimlich Institute Foundation, Inc. - General Correspondence (Reel 87, Frame 577)
  - Hektoen Institute - Denied Proposal 89-15 (Reel 87, Frame 585)
  - Helicon Foundation - Denied Proposals 86-7, 86-43 (Reel 87, Frame 597)
  - Henry Ford Hospital - General Correspondence (Reel 87, Frame 614)
  - (Carl J.) Herzog Foundation, Inc. - General Correspondence (Reel 87, Frame 618)
  - Hillcrest Medical Center - Denied Proposals 86-33, 88-43, 88-71 (Reel 87, Frame 647)
  - University of Hong Kong - Denied Proposal 84-228 (Reel 87, Frame 716)
  - (Bob) Hope International Heart Research Institute - Denied Proposal 85-108 (Reel 87, Frame 721)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery - Denied Proposal 89-68 (Reel 87, Frame 759)
  - Houghton College - Denied Proposal 85-2 (Reel 87, Frame 782)
  - House Ear Institute - Denied Proposal 88-82 (Reel 87, Frame 794)
  - University of Houston - Denied Proposals 86-28, 86-173, 87-58, 89-94, 92-25 (Reel 87, Frame 812)
  - Howard University - General Correspondence (Reel 87, Frame 954)
  - Human Genome Organisation (HUGO) - Denied Proposal 91-39 (Reel 87, Frame 971)
  - Hunter College - Denied Proposal 85-167 (Reel 87, Frame 980)
  - (Fred) Hutchinson Cancer Research Center - Denied Proposals 85-45, 85-51 (Reel 87, Frame 992)
  - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign - Denied Proposals 86-18, 86-72, 86-167, 91-35 (Reel 87, Frame 1011)
  - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign - Research Program Grant - Grant 92-20 (Reel 88, Frame 1)
  - University of Illinois College of Medicine, Chicago - General Correspondence (Reel 88, Frame 217)
  - Illinois College of Medicine - Denied Proposals 89-46, 89-63, 94-16 (Reel 88, Frame 261)
  - Illinois Institute of Technology - Denied Proposal 93-4 (Reel 88, Frame 326)
  - Indiana University - Denied Proposals 84-30, 86-165, 87-38, 89-35, 91-11, 92-7 (Reel 88, Frame 349)
  - Institute for Advanced Study - Denied Proposal 95-11 (Reel 88, Frame 456)
  - Institute for Basic Research in Developmental Disabilities - Denied Proposal 85-187 (Reel 88, Frame 495)
  - Institute for Developmental Research - General Correspondence (Reel 88, Frame 514)
  - Intersearch Institute, Inc. - General Correspondence (Reel 88, Frame 516)
  - University of Iowa, Iowa City - Denied Proposals 85-103, 85-134, 85-225, 85-256, 85-260, 86-130, 86-170, 87-29, 87-43, 87-46, 87-64, 87-68, 89-27, 89-53 (Reel 88, Frame 532)
  - Iowa State University - Denied Proposals 85-75, 85-79, 85-87, 85-144, 87-31 (Reel 88, Frame 744)
  - Jackson Laboratory - General Correspondence (Reel 88, Frame 776)
  - Jackson Laboratory - Grant 85-19 (Reel 88, Frame 804)
  - Jackson Memorial Foundation, Inc. - General Correspondence (Reel 88, Frame 1138)
  - Jacksonville University - General Correspondence (Reel 88, Frame 1142)
  - Johns Hopkins University - General Correspondence (Reel 89, Frame 1)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Denied Proposals 85-8, 85-37, 86-70, 87-9, 87-11, 90-48 (Reel 89, Frame 108)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Grant 84-6 (Reel 89, Frame 243)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Grant 89-10 (Reel 89, Frame 418)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Grant 94-4 (Reel 89, Frame 463)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-19 (Reel 89, Frame 606)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Grant 96-4 (Reel 89, Frame 714)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine - Grant 89-9 (Reel 89, Frame 759)
  - (W. Alton) Jones Cell Science Center, Inc. - Denied Proposals 85-177, 89-90 (Reel 89, Frame 952)
  - Jones Institute for Reproductive Medicine - Denied Proposal 89-57 (Reel 89, Frame 986)
  - Joslin Diabetes Center - Research Program Grant - Grant 93-4 (Reel 90, Frame 1)
  - Kaiser Foundation Hospitals - Denied Proposal 85-91 (Reel 90, Frame 248)
  - University of Kansas, Lawrence - Denied Proposal 85-94 (Reel 90, Frame 261)
  - Kansas State University - Denied Proposal 85-79 (Reel 90, Frame 273)
  - Keen Ager Corporation - Denied Proposal 85-36 (Reel 90, Frame 288)
  - Kennedy Krieger Institute - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-11 (Reel 90, Frame 303)
  - Kent State University - Denied Proposal 85-212 (Reel 90, Frame 398)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - General Correspondence (Reel 90, Frame 413)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Denied Proposals 86-25, 88-81, 90-27, 90-60, 91-22 (Reel 90, Frame 817)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Grant 84-14 (Reel 91, Frame 1)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Grant 85-21 (Reel 91, Frame 233)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Grant 91-55 (Reel 91, Frame 431)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-32 (Reel 91, Frame 463)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Grant 96-6 (Reel 91, Frame 624)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Lucille Parker Markey Cancer Center - General Correspondence (Reel 91, Frame 666)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Lucille Parker Markey Cancer Center - Grant 84-3 (Reel 92, Frame 1)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Lucille Parker Markey Cancer Center - Grant 98-5 (Reel 92, Frame 301)
  - University of Kentucky, Lexington - Maxwell H. Gluck Equine Research Center - Grant 88-64 (Reel 92, Frame 324)
  - Keystone Center - Denied Proposals 91-37, 92-57 (Reel 92, Frame 654)
  - La Jolla Cancer Research Foundation - Denied Proposals 86-61, 88-56, 95-14 (Reel 92, Frame 676)
  - La Jolla Cancer Research Foundation - Research Program Grant - Grant 92-9 (Reel 92, Frame 706)
  - Lankenau Medical Research Center - Denied Proposal 88-76 (Reel 92, Frame 914)
  - La Rabida Children's Hospital and Research Center - General Correspondence (Reel 92, Frame 943)
  - Life Sciences Research Foundation - Denied Proposal 94-24 (Reel 93, Frame 1)
  - Life Sciences Research Foundation - Grant 85-23 (Reel 93, Frame 123)
  - Linus Pauling Institute of Science and Medicine - Denied Proposals 86-78, 92-14 (Reel 93, Frame 215)
  - Loma Linda University - General Correspondence (Reel 93, Frame 254)
  - Louisiana State University - Denied Proposals 85-205, 85-209, 85-233, 86-175, 90-13, 90-56 (Reel 93, Frame 265)
  - University of Louisville - Denied Proposals 89-38, 89-59 (Reel 93, Frame 312)
  - Loyola University - Denied Proposals 85-193, 92-17 (Reel 93, Frame 357)
  - Mankind Research Foundation, Inc. - Denied Proposals 86-42, 88-52 (Reel 93, Frame 403)
  - Manteuil-Brutlag, Dr. Simone - Denied Proposal 93-22 (Reel 93, Frame 416)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory (Wood's Hole) - Denied Proposals 90-41, 90-66, 95-5 (Reel 93, Frame 445)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory (Wood's Hole) - Grant 85-18 (Reel 93, Frame 496)
  - Marquette University - Denied Proposals 86-45, 88-64 (Reel 93, Frame 713)
  - Marshall University - Denied Proposals 89-56, 91-21 (Reel 93, Frame 749)
  - University of Maryland - Denied Proposals 86-37, 86-38, 86-46, 86-101, 92-15, 92-28 (Reel 93, Frame 783)
  - University of Maryland Biotechnology Institute - Research Program Grant - Grant 95-31 (Reel 93, Frame 889)
  - University of Massachusetts, Amherst - Denied Proposals 86-103, 88-57, 94-37 (Reel 94, Frame 1)
  - Massachusetts Corporation for Educational Telecommunications - Denied Proposal 92-40 (Reel 94, Frame 96)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Denied Proposal 85-46 (Reel 94, Frame 120)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Grant 93-1 (Reel 94, Frame 143)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - General Correspondence (Reel 94, Frame 332)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Denied Proposals 85-234, 85-248, 86-118, 92-39, 93-13 (Reel 94, Frame 385)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Grant 84-7 (Reel 94, Frame 462)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Grant 91-7 (Reel 94, Frame 613)
  - University of Massachusetts Medical Center - General Correspondence (Reel 94, Frame 914)
  - University of Massachusetts Medical Center - Denied Proposals 85-173, 85-258 (Reel 94, Frame 921)
  - University of Massachusetts Medical Center - Grant 95-3 (Reel 94, Frame 940)
  - Mayo Foundation - Denied Proposal 92-20 (Reel 95, Frame 1)
  - Medical Biology Institute - Denied Proposal 90-21 (Reel 95, Frame 26)
  - Medical Education for South African Blacks, Inc. - Denied Proposal 89-67 (Reel 95, Frame 46)
  - Medlantic Research Foundation - Denied Proposal 88-20 (Reel 95, Frame 54)
  - Meharry Medical College - General Correspondence (Reel 95, Frame 75)
  - Meharry Medical College - Denied Proposal 89-19 (Reel 95, Frame 92)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Denied Proposals 85-124, 85-140 (Reel 95, Frame 165)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Grant 91-17 (Reel 95, Frame 212)
  - Mercer University - Denied Proposals 85-194, 89-77, 90-1 (Reel 95, Frame 415)
  - Methodist Hospital - Denied Proposal 85-174 (Reel 95, Frame 467)
  - University of Miami - General Correspondence (Reel 95, Frame 480)
  - University of Miami - Denied Proposals 84-42, 85-42, 85-53, 85-85, 85-93, 85-95, 85-241, 86-15, 86-98, 86-153 (Reel 95, Frame 577)
  - University of Miami - Grant 84-15 (Reel 96, Frame 1)
  - University of Miami - Grant 88-22 (Reel 96, Frame 306)
  - University of Miami - Grant 95-4 (Reel 96, Frame 520)
  - University of Miami - Warren Wright Adolescent Medicine Program - General Correspondence (Reel 96, Frame 685)
  - Miami Children's Hospital Foundation - Denied Proposal 90-70 (Reel 96, Frame 775)
  - Miami Heart Institute - General Correspondence (Reel 96, Frame 885)
  - Miami Heart Institute - Denied Proposal 86-150 (Reel 96, Frame 914)
  - Miami Heart Institute - Grant 84-1 (Reel 96, Frame 937)
  - Miami Project to Cure Paralysis - General Correspondence (Reel 96, Frame 992)
  - Miami University - Denied Proposal 85-152 (Reel 96, Frame 1063)
  - Miami Veteran's Administration Hospital - General Correspondence (Reel 96, Frame 1071)
  - Michael Reese Hospital and Medical Center - Denied Proposal 85-86 (Reel 96, Frame 1074)
  - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Denied Proposals 85-208, 85-257, 86-36, 87-54 (Reel 97, Frame 1)